Now I've taken weakness as my ally
I can fly to the highest heights
If I would just stop here
all I've lost would lose its luster
If you were lost out somewhere
at the same time my heart is shaken
Id have no way to find you
your kindness, or even your strength
I know
It's time for the dawn!
My peak performance
blow straight past in a blast, yeah
You'll be left frozen with laughs
The days of pain left in the past, let's hope
As I make foes of the world
I'm bracing myself upon shaking legs, yeah
Just keep me going for a few more steps
Now, this is the comeback, the time to awaken is now
Halt, Luffy!
I know ya got this, Momo!
"Get Onigashima out of your way"?
I...
I cannot do it!
Time to finish this!
I hear you, loud and clear.
And I accept!
That burns!
That's right.
You can let go of me.
'Cause I'm not going anywhere.
Tell me, Straw Hat... Did you know?
That twenty years ago...
...the hero of this country
burned to death?
The Land of Wano has been
lawless ever since!
And now, you are the heroes
the people have waited twenty years for!
Flame Dragon Torch!
That hand of yours will never touch me!
It will melt into nothing!
Luffy!
Meltin'...
Yeah, as if!
The old guy taught me how to
attack without touchin' ya!
You call it "Haki,"
but we in the Land of Wano call it "Ryuo."
Don't strain yourself, now!
Flow the Haki from the parts of your body
that don't need it into your fists.
I'm smashin' ya down all the way
to the bottom of hell!
Gum-Gum...
Rising Dragon!
Bajrang...
...Gun!
Flame Bagua!
Huh? What's happening?!
What's going on up there?!
Straw Hat-san!
Go!
Please, Straw Hat-san!
Go, Straw Hat!
Please!
Take him down!
Do it!
We're begging you!
I'm begging you! Please!
I leave the rest to
the lot of ye!
Run! To Kuri!
Oden... sama!
Do not look back!
Run!
There is only one place
those filthy samurai could have gone!
To Kuri!
The heir of Kozuki is in the castle!
Kill them all!
Wipe the name Kozuki from history!
Slaughter them!
Every last one!
He has a child?
I'll put an end to this.
Stop!
Haven't you done enough to the Kozu
Out of my way!
You have my permission to fire
at anyone who dares defy the Shogun!
Let them feel the depths of
the Kurozumi's hatred!
Take this!
Suffer!
Filthy commoners, worshipping
the very ground the Kozuki stand on!
What of Oden's wife?
She was confirmed dead in Bakura Town.
No one else escaped from Oden Castle.
The Kozuki Clan has been
thoroughly wiped out!
Now I present you
with a choice, Daimyo!
Do you choose to stand alongside us
and bring Wano to greatness...
or do you choose war?!
Why even ask...
...when the answer is so obvious?!
The Kozuki Clan is our only Shogun!
Avenge Oden!
Protect the Land of Wano
till you breathe your last!
Fear no enemy! Stand and fight!
Blast Breath!
No!
How utterly pitiful!
"The resolve of the samurai"?
Does the word "samurai"
no longer hold any meaning?
Pathetic, weak samurai!
You have mocked me, looked down on me,
and now you lay defeated before me!
Weaklings cannot protect anything!
Now heed my words, fools!
As of today,
Kurozumi is the law of the land!
Serves you right!
Bring me every man of working age!
Daddy!
Give me back my Daddy!
Don't take him away!
D-Don't shoot!
Honey!
I-I'm okay....
Daddy!
The whole country will be
a weapons factory!
Quit nappin' on the job.
Work till you drop dead!
We can't grow any food...
with soil like this!
I can't take it anymore...
I'm sorry...
We have no water to drink... No food...
What will become of this country?
Somebody, help! Please!
Won't somebody save us?!
If you wanna see tomorrow,
then get to work, miserable vermin!
That material's way more important than you!
You break it, you die!
Go ahead and scream if you want!
But no help's coming!
This country's closed off from the world!
I can't take it anymore.
I'd rather die...
Don't jump the gun.
Winter's coming...
A long, long winter...
Believe...
...what Toki-sama said.
Look at them, Kaido!
The lowlives actually ate
the defective Smiles!
Eat! Eat!
Laugh!
And follow in Ebisu Town's footsteps!
Laugh like imbeciles, even if you're starving!
Even if your family dies before your eyes!
It is a fitting life for
maggots such as yourselves!
I'll grace you with a life of
never-ending smiles!
Time for a feast!
Eat and drink...
...to your hearts' content!
My Mommy and Daddy are dead!
Komurasaki!
Everything was going my way!
Everything!
You're a lowly tramp who
willingly offered herself up at the Pleasure Hall!
Komurasaki!
You're coming with me to Hell!
And there, we will share
another drink, you and I!
Do not underestimate
the grudge of the Kurozumi Clan!
Foxfire Kin'emon
and the Red Scabbards...
I welcome their challenge,
should we ever stand face to face!
I shall slay them all
in one swift stroke!
Alas, such a dreadful sight.
from this
hell.
"Get Onigashima out of your way"?
What should I do?
It is simply...
...not possible for me!
I cannot!
I have tried so many times,
but it is simply not possible!
Mononosuke
You are to leap
twenty years into the future,
and return the Kozuki Clan
to greatness!
Mother!
Worry not. I know you can do it.
And all shall know just how much
you have sacrificed for them.
Hiyori!
Father!
I leave the rest to you!
If I falter here...
will disgrace the Kozuki name!
Momonosuke-kun!
They all depend on me!
I refuse to surrender!
There! There they are!
Kin'emon! Kiku!
You're still alive, right?!
Don't you die on me!
You hear that?!
Don't you dare die on me!
Please, Straw Hat...
Take down Kaido!
As long as Kaido falls...
Please...
Straw Hat Man...
Our 20-year battle...
Kaido must be brought down...
As long as Kaido remains...
...our battle will never be over!
You've done well...
Done well, fighting to get this far!
But...
...you can't change the world!
I plundered everything
with my own two hands...
...and rose to be an Emperor of the Sea.
You're the man, Kaido!
You're making us even stronger!
No one in this world...
...can beat me!
You don't know anything, do you?
Our country can't just stop going to war...
We have to win and loot valuables
so we can pay the Heavenly Tribute...
Otherwise, the world'll strip
our human rights away!
To this country,
we're nothing but tools!
Why does everyone bow down
to those "Celestial Dragons"?
You have been drafted.
And you will join the Navy!
Why should I want to be
the Government's lapdog?!
You're more than
my country can handle.
Shut up! Don't tell me what to do!
Don't mess with me!
You're all gonna pay!
If you turn Kaido over to us,
your country will be granted
the right to participate in the Reverie...
I am not your bargaining chip!
Kaido escaped!
He got out again?!
That rat bastard!
He gets caught every time he gets hungry!
Our prison ship isn't one big galley!
So strong!
Who is he?!
Hey! This says he's still fifteen!
This bounty's
way too high for a kid!
He's a monster!
Hey, stinkin' brat.
Wanna be a pirate?
Rocks said he wanted to see you.
How 'bout it?
Kaido joined the Rocks Pirates!
They're invincible now!
Big trouble, Kaido!
C'mon! We're headed to God Valley!
What?!
The Rocks Pirates split up?!
What kind of joke is that?!
They had all those monsters!
I heard some Navy sailor
named Garp defeated them!
They must've had a falling out!
They had no idea how to work as a team!
Where the hell'd you go, Kaido?!
You dare spit in my face, you freak!!
It's been ten years since that incident...
You're the avatar of military might, Kaido!
Throughout human history,
resorting to armed conflict has solved
all sorts of problems around the world.
Hardly a surprise...
...because humans are animals!
It's only natural for the weak
to fall victim to the strong!
You're totally right.
The remnants of the Rocks Pirates
will come into power!
Weapons are what speak loudest
in the world we live in!
I got something good for you...
Those pampered authorities,
who have only ever known peace...
...were merely lucky enough
to be born as nobles!
Drag them off their thrones,
down to the battlefield!
That's what I call equality and freedom!
A person's worth
is determined only by war!
Ya know I'm gonna win!
I don't know where he heard it from,
but Yamato mentioned Joyboy's name.
Apparently, Oden wanted to welcome Joyboy,
and that's why he called for the borders to open.
If he's the same guy
you're waiting for, King,
then I know exactly who Joyboy is.
Do not lose heart, Momonosuke!
He will win! Luffy will win!
Yes, indeed!
The people of Wano all depend on you!
Do it, Momonosuke-kun!
Come forth, Flame Clouds!
Heed my call!
The hell's that noise?
Robin-san...!
Quell this inferno!
Help!
Save them all!
Water of Zou!
Water?!
They's fallin' like raindrops!
Look! Isn't that...?!
We will make it outta here!
Usopp?!
Kin'emon!
O-Kiku-chan!
Noooo!
You have been...
You have been so brave and strong....
...for all these years,
Hiyori-sama.
Sorry 'bout that, Zoro...
Hey, don't y'all get washed off, now!
Where'd this water come from?!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Sanji-san!
O-Somechwan!
What is happening inside Onigashima?!
The Flame Clouds are dispersing!
No! Onigashima is plummeting!
Come forth, Flame Clouds!
Amazing!
Spectacular work, Momonsuke-kun!
Now, go!
Aye-aye! Roger that!
Go!
I will conquer Wano,
and then the world itself!
Now, what kind of world
do think you can create...
you
...Straw Hat?!
I'll make...
Luffy!
A world where all my pals...
...get to eat...
...til they're full!
Kaido!
King.
I know exactly who Joyboy is.
Who is it?
He's the man who'll defeat me someday!
Guess he'll never show, then.
"Time's up"
Someone said again, with a laugh
Fine then, hide-and-seek playtime...
...is over
Let's go, come on (We can see it soon)
Let your heart beat out
and things will change (We can see it soon)
Grow strong, you have time
Lift up that dream
The overflowing loneliness can't sustain me alone
We were so free in our younger days
What a dumb dream
...to live
Shining a light on uncharted ways
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
Together, we can go and fly